Lives are on the line
The Commuter is a action, thriller, mystery film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra.
A businessman, on his daily commute home, gets unwittingly caught up in a criminal
conspiracy that threatens not only his life but the lives of those around him.
Michael MacCauley, played by Liam Neeson.
Alex Murphy, played by Patrick Wilson.
Captain Hawthorne, played by Sam Neill.
Walt, played by Jonathan Banks.
Joanna, played by Vera Farmiga.
Karen MacCauley, played by Elizabeth McGovern.
The Commuter is a 2018 action thriller film directed by Jaume Collet-Serra and
written by Byron Willinger, Philip de Blasi and Ryan Engle.
The film stars Liam Neeson, Vera Farmiga, Patrick Wilson,
Jonathan Banks, Florence Pugh, and Sam Neill.
It follows a man who is unwittingly recruited into a murder conspiracy after
meeting a mysterious woman while on his daily train commute.
The film premiered in New York City on January 8, 2018, and was theatrically released in the United States on
January 12, 2018, by Lionsgate, and on January 19, 2018, in the United Kingdom by StudioCanal.
The film grossed $119 million worldwide and received mixed reviews from critics, who called it similar to Neeson
and Collet-Serra's previous film, Non-Stop, but praised Neeson's performance and the genre thrills.
The tone is mind_bending and intense.